Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Student Newspapers Collection
1916-2018
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua809
2282 Digital Files
326 captures
17.47 GB
The University at Albany, SUNY student newspapers (State College News,, State University News, Albany Student Press), from 1916-present. Issues from the years 1916-1985 and 2015-present are available online. Additional issues are only available in-person.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical History
The Albany Student Press (ASP) has been the name of the weekly student newspaper of the State University of New York at Albany (University at Albany, SUNY) since February 14, 1964 (Vol. L, no. 1). The ASP and its predecessors since 1916 have carried news of student events, opinion, organizations, and since the 1960s reviews of movies, recordings, and more recently, short literary pieces. The ASP is currently a weekly (while school is in session) publication, though for much of its existence (Fall, 1964 – Spring, 1996) it was published twice a week, on Tuesday and Friday. By the fall of 1996 the ASP was published only on Friday, and after the spring of 2003 the publication date shifted to Monday. The ASP is the successor to the briefly titled weekly student newspaper, the State University News, February 8, 1963 -- January 10, 1964, (Vol. XLIX, no. 2 – XLIX, no. 27).
The State University News and the Albany Student Press are the direct successors of the weekly State College News,, October 4, 1916 -- January 11, 1963 (Vol. 1, no. 1 – sic XXXIX, correctly [LXIX], no. 1). The State College News, was the first true (during the school year) student newspaper published at the then New York State College for Teachers. News of student life and events, faculty life and projects, and alumni news prior to 1916 was carried in the monthly The Normal College Echo, subsequently The Echo, from June 1892 – May-June, 1916 (Vol. 1, no. 1 — Vol. XXV, no. 9). The Normal College Echo and its successor, The Echo, were a combination literary magazine, student and alumni newspaper. After the creation of the State College News, in fall of 1916, The Echo remained the school's student literary magazine, and continued to carry faculty and alumni news until the creation of the Alumni Quarterly in 1919. The Echo also continued to carry some student news, particularly items of interest to alumni/ae, until 1919 when it became a strictly literary magazine.
Scope and Contents
Contains a run of the student newspapers published at the State Normal School, the State College for Teachers, SUNY Albany, and the University at Albany, SUNY.
Arrangement of the Collection
The Student Newspaper Collection is divided into series by decade, and then suberies by publication year.
Newspapers; Digital Files; UAlbany Student Groups; College student newspapers and periodicals; Wages -- New York (State); College student newspapers and periodicals--New York (State)--Albany; New York State Normal College; New York State College for Teachers; State University of New York at Albany; State College News,; Albany Student Press
- State College News, 1910s, 1916-1919; 1; 96 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1916, 12 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 1, 1916 October 4; 2.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 2, 1916 October 11; 2.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 3, 1916 October 18; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 4, 1916 October 25; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 5, 1916 November 1; 1.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 6, 1916 November 8; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 7, 1916 November 15; 1.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 8, 1916 November 22; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 9, 1916 November 29; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 10, 1916 December 6; 1.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 11, 1916 December 13; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 12, 1916 December 20; 1.53 MB
  - State College News, 1917, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 13, 1917 January 10; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 14, 1917 January 17; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 15, 1917 February 14; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 16, 1917 February 21; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 17, 1917 February 28; 1.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 18, 1917 March 7; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 19, 1917 March 14; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 20, 1917 March 21; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 21, 1917 March 28; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 22, 1917 April 18; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 23, 1917 May 2; 1.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 24, 1917 May 16; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 25, 1917 June 13; 1.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 1, 1917 September 19; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 2, 1917 September 26; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 3, 1917 October 3; 1.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 4, 1917 October 10; 1.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 5, 1917 October 17; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 6, 1917 October 24; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 7, 1917 October 31; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 8, 1917 November 7; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 9, 1917 November 14; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 10, 1917 November 21; 1.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 11, 1917 November 28; 2.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 12, 1917 December 12; 1.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 13, 1917 December 19; 1.64 MB
  - State College News, 1918, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 14, 1918 January 9; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 15, 1918 January 16; 1.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 16, 1918 February 6; 1.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 17, 1918 February 13; 1.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 18, 1918 February 20; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 19, 1918 February 27; 1.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 20, 1918 March 6; 1.76 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 21, 1918 March 13; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 22, 1918 March 20; 1.66 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 23, 1918 March 27; 1.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 24, 1918 April 17; 1.76 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 25, 1918 April 24; 1.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 26, 1918 May 1; 1.83 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 27, 1918 May 7; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 28, 1918 May 15; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 29, 1918 May 22; 1.79 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 30, 1918 May 29; 1.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 31, 1918 June 15; 4.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 1, 1918 September 18; 1.88 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 2, 1918 September 26; 1.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 3, 1918 October 3; 0.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 4, 1918 October 10; 1.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 5, 1918 November 14; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 6, 1918 November 21; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 7, 1918 November 28; 1.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 8, 1918 December 5; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 9, 1918 December 12; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 10, 1918 December 19; 1.64 MB
  - State College News, 1919, 30 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 14, 1919 February 6; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 15, 1919 February 13; 1.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 16, 1919 February 20; 1.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 17, 1919 February 27; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 18, 1919 March 6; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 19, 1919 March 13; 1.62 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 20, 1919 March 20; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 21, 1919 March 27; 1.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 22, 1919 April 3; 1.80 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 23, 1919 April 10; 1.84 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 24, 1919 May 8; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 25, 1919 May 14; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 26, 1919 May 17; 6.06 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 27, 1919 May 22; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 28, 1919 May 29; 1.72 MB
    - State College News, Volume 3, Number 30, 1919 June 14; 1.71 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 1, 1919 September 19; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 2, 1919 September 25; 1.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 3, 1919 October 2; 1.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 4, 1919 October 9; 1.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 5, 1919 October 16; 1.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 6, 1919 October 23; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 7, 1919 October 30; 1.31 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 8, 1919 November 6; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 9, 1919 November 13; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 10, 1919 November 20; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 11, 1919 November 26; 1.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 12, 1919 December 4; 1.20 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 13, 1919 December 11; 1.65 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 14, 1919 December 18; 1.61 MB
- State College News, 1920s, 1920-1929; 2; 315 Digital Files
  - State College News, 1920, 27 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 15, 1920 January 15; 2.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 16, 1920 February 6; 2.18 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 17, 1920 February 12; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 18, 1920 February 22; 1.74 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 19, 1920 February 26; 1.76 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 20, 1920 March 4; 1.22 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 21, 1920 March 11; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 22, 1920 March 18; 1.91 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 23, 1920 March 25; 6.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 24, 1920 April 22; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 25, 1920 April 29; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 26, 1920 May 6; 1.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 27, 1920 May 13; 0.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 28, 1920 May 20; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 4, Number 29, 1920 June 4; 1.95 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 1, 1920 September 30; 1.70 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 2, 1920 October 7; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 3, 1920 October 14; 1.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 4, 1920 October 21; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 5, 1920 October 28; 1.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 6, 1920 November 4; 1.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 7, 1920 November 11; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 8, 1920 November 18; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 9, 1920 November 24; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 10, 1920 December 2; 1.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 11, 1920 December 9; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 12, 1920 December 16; 1.50 MB
  - State College News, 1921, 32 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 13, 1921 January 13; 1.28 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 14, 1921 January 20; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 15, 1921 February 10; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 16, 1921 February 17; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 17, 1921 February 24; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 18, 1921 March 3; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 19, 1921 March 10; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 20, 1921 March 17; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 21, 1921 March 24; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 22, 1921 April 1; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 23, 1921 April 21; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 5, Number 24, 1921 April 28; 6.15 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 1, 1921 July 5; 1.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 2, 1921 July 11; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 3, 1921 July 18; 1.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 4, 1921 July 25; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 5, 1921 August 1; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 1, Number 6, 1921 August 9; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 1, 1921 September 20; 1.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 2, 1921 September 27; 1.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 3, 1921 October 3; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 4, 1921 October 10; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 5, 1921 October 17; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 6, 1921 October 24; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 7, 1921 October 31; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 8, 1921 November 7; 1.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 9, 1921 November 14; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 10, 1921 November 21; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 11, 1921 November 28; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 12, 1921 December 5; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 13, 1921 December 12; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 14, 1921 December 19; 1.33 MB
  - State College News, 1922, 33 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 15, 1922 January 9; 1.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 16, 1922 January 16; 1.21 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 17, 1922 January 23; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 18, 1922 January 30; 1.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 19, 1922 February 6; 1.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 20, 1922 February 13; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 21, 1922 February 20; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 22, 1922 February 27; 1.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 23, 1922 March 6; 1.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 24, 1922 March 13; 1.61 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 25, 1922 March 20; 1.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 26, 1922 March 27; 1.30 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 27, 1922 April 3; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 29, 1922 May 1; 1.32 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 30, 1922 May 8; 2.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 31, 1922 May 15; 1.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 6, Number 32, 1922 May 22; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 1, 1922 July 10; 1.31 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 3, 1922 July 25; 1.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 4, 1922 August 1; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 5, 1922 August 8; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 2, Number 6, 1922 August 15; 1.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 2, 1922 September 28; 1.29 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 3, 1922 October 5; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 4, 1922 October 12; 1.27 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 5, 1922 October 19; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 6, 1922 October 26; 1.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 7, 1922 November 2; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 8, 1922 November 9; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 9, 1922 November 16; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 10, 1922 November 24; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 11, 1922 December 8; 1.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 12, 1922 December 15; 1.49 MB
  - State College News, 1923, 26 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 13, 1923 January 12; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 14, 1923 January 19; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 15, 1923 February 5; 1.57 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 16, 1923 February 9; 1.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 17, 1923 February 16; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 18, 1923 February 23; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 19, 1923 March 2; 1.60 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 20, 1923 March 9; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 23, 1923 April 13; 1.26 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 24, 1923 April 20; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 25, 1923 April 27; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 26, 1923 May 4; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 27, 1923 May 11; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 28, 1923 May 18; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 7, Number 29, 1923 June 8; 7.78 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 1, 1923 September 28; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 2, 1923 October 5; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 3, 1923 October 12; 1.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 4, 1923 October 19; 1.63 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 5, 1923 October 26; 1.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 6, 1923 November 2; 1.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 7, 1923 November 9; 1.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 8, 1923 November 16; 1.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 9, 1923 November 23; 1.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 10, 1923 November 7; 1.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 11, 1923 November 14; 1.58 MB
  - State College News, 1924, 30 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 12, 1924 January 11; 1.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 13, 1924 January 18; 1.52 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 14, 1924 February 1; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 15, 1924 February 8; 1.59 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 16, 1924 February 15; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 17, 1924 February 22; 1.56 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 18, 1924 February 29; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 19, 1924 March 3; 1.64 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 20, 1924 March 14; 1.68 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 21, 1924 March 21; 1.69 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 22, 1924 March 28; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 23, 1924 April 4; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 24, 1924 April 11; 1.73 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 25, 1924 May 2; 1.67 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 26, 1924 May 9; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 27, 1924 May 16; 1.53 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 28, 1924 May 23; 1.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 8, Number 29, 1924 June; 5.81 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 1, 1924 September 26; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 2, 1924 October 3; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 3, 1924 October 10; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 4, 1924 October 17; 1.54 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 5, 1924 October 24; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 6, 1924 October 31; 1.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 7, 1924 November 7; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 8, 1924 November 14; 1.55 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 9, 1924 November 21; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 10, 1924 December 5; 1.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 11, 1924 December 12; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 12, 1924 December 19; 1.65 MB
  - State College News, 1925, 28 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 13, 1925 January 16; 1.58 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 14, 1925 January 30; 1.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 15, 1925 February 6; 1.47 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 16, 1925 February 13; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 17, 1925 February 20; 1.42 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 18, 1925 February 27; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 19, 1925 March 6; 1.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 20, 1925 March 13; 1.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 21, 1925 March 20; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 22, 1925 March 27; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 23, 1925 April 3; 1.44 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 24, 1925 April 24; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 27, 1925 May 14; 1.43 MB
    - State College News, Volume 9, Number 28, 1925 May 29; 3.89 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 1, 1925 October 2; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 2, 1925 October 6; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 3, 1925 October 9; 1.49 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 4, 1925 October 16; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 5, 1925 October 23; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 6, 1925 October 30; 1.46 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 7, 1925 November 3; 1.50 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 8, 1925 November 6; 1.34 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 9, 1925 November 13; 1.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 10, 1925 November 20; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 11, 1925 November 25; 1.51 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 12, 1925 December 4; 1.48 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 13, 1925 December 11; 1.36 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 14, 1925 December 18; 1.48 MB
  - State College News, 1926, 32 Digital Files
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 15, 1926 January 15; 1.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 16, 1926 January 22; 1.41 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 17, 1926 January 29; 2.45 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 18, 1926 February 12; 1.33 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 19, 1926 February 19; 1.40 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 20, 1926 February 26; 1.39 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 21, 1926 March 5; 1.37 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 22, 1926 March 12; 1.35 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 23, 1926 March 19; 1.38 MB
    - State College News, Volume 10, Number 24, 1926 March 26; 1.30 MB